http://www.christianaid.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Christian Aid Mission is committed to protecting your privacy and your personal information. We do not share, sell, or rent your personal information to others. Your privacy is very important to us, and we want you to be assured that our privacy practices are held to the highest standard.
When submitting your information over our website, your information is protected and secure.
As with most other internet websites, Christianaid.org uses visitors’ IP addresses to gather broad demographic information and to improve our website services.
Email Notifications
In order to receive emails from us, you must provide Christian Aid Mission with your email address. Your email address will only be used to communicate with you. We will not give this out to any third-party organizations at any time or for any reason. In the event that you do not wish to receive emails from us, simply click the bottom of the email to easily unsubscribe.
Online Donations
Be assured that the personal information including credit card or other information that you share is collected through securely encrypted web forms and protected by up-to-date security procedures.
Christian Aid Mission seeks to establish a witness for Christ in every nation by assisting indigenous ministries based in areas of poverty and persecution, giving priority to ministries sharing the gospel of Jesus Christ with unreached people groups. Today, we work with hundreds of indigenous ministries in eight regions of the world that share the gospel with more than 2,000 unreached people groups.
P.O. Box 9037, Charlottesville, Virginia 22906
info@christianaid.org
(434)-977-5650
Facebook-f
Twitter
Instagram
Main Menu
About Us
Contact Us
Mission Insider
Privacy Policy
Prayerline
Sign up for Ministry Updates
Sign Up
Christian Aid Mission is committed to using the funds our supporters entrust to us with the utmost integrity and efficiency. We seek to glorify God and honor our supporters by being wise stewards of our resources with the goal of establishing a witness for Christ in every nation.
2020 Platinum Seal of Transparency
GuideStar a service of Candid
2020 Platinum Seal of Transparency
GuideStar a service of Candid
Copyright © 2011-2020 Christian Aid Mission. All Rights Reserved.
CamWp
